http://innerexpansionblog.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for InnerExpansion.com (”IEW”). We reserve the right to modify the information contained herein at anytime without prior notice. If we do make changes to our privacy policies, we will modify this page accordingly. This site and all information and materials on it are provided to you “as is” without warranty of any kind.
YOUR USE OF THIS SITE, OR YOUR PROVISION TO US OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION, CONSTITUTES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THESE TERMS AND ANY SUBSEQUENT CHANGES TO THESE TERMS; DO NOT USE THIS SITE OR PROVIDE INFORMATION IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS.
Normal Browsing
As with many websites, we collect certain information, even when you are not logged in. When you browse, read, or download information from IEW, data is collected by IEW, including but not limited to your IP address, email address, URL request, browser type, and date and time of your request.
We analyze traffic to IEW in various ways, including using a service called Google Analytics. (Google Analytics is subject to the privacy policy of Google, Inc., which you can find on their website.) We use this information to generate statistics and measure site activity to improve the usefulness of the site to our visitors. Unless you affirmatively provide additional information to us, we do not collect or store personally identifiable information such as name, mailing address, email address, phone number, or social security number.
We collect the IP addresses of visitors, time of access, browser type, and web pages visited. We collect this information on an aggregate basis only. For example, we track which pages are most popular among visitors as a whole. We do not track information on which pages an individual user visits. We do not collect any other information without your knowledge and permission.
Information You Provide
IEW requests personally identifiable information if and when you register for an account. Information may be used or requested to perform research, improve usability of the site, administer mailing lists or online communities, or other activities related to IEW’s mission or services. This information may include, but is not limited to, personal names, e-mail addresses, and location.
Disclosure of Information
Available log records, account information, and all data stored on servers hosting this website and blog may be accessed by our system administrators. In the event that we are required by law (including a court order) to disclose the information you submit, we will do so.
Cookies
We may use session cookies when you visit our website while your browser is open, or while you are logged into our site. To facilitate our registration and login functions, we may use cookies to recognize when you return to our website. If you do not logout of your account, these cookies allow us to keep track of your username and password so that you do not have to resubmit the information to log into your account. If others will be using your computer, you should log out of your account so that your logon information is cleared.
Children’s Privacy
IEW content is intended for adults and we will not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a child under age 13 who you believe has submitted personal information to IEW or this site, please contact us immediately.
Posting
Posting or updating content is a public action, and all content may be publicly visible. All content may be retained for restorative, archival, or research purposes by IEW. Editing or deleting content may alter the displayed state of the content, and may permanently delete the content from the website or its accompanying blog.
Security
IEW has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However, your confidential use of this site cannot be guaranteed by IEW. IEW shall not be responsible for any harm that you or any person may suffer as a result of a breach of confidentiality in respect to your use of this site or any information you transmitted to this site.
Other Websites
Material on this website may link to independently run websites outside of the InnerExpansion.com domain. IEW is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of any websites you visit from this website and its accompanying blog.
This Privacy Policy was created and posted on May 13, 2010.
Search for:
Proudly powered by WordPress.
